Guide to the United Brewery Workers Local 267 Records, 1936-1959 AIS.1984.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Brewery Workers Local 267 Records
1936-1959
ULS Archives & Special Collections
International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America. Local 267 (Logansport, Pa.)
AIS.1984.11
1.25 Linear Feet (1 box)
The International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Local 267 in Logansport, Pennsylvania, began as United Distillery Workers of North America, Local 942 at Logansport Distilling Company, Inc. This collection includes information from 1936 to 1959 regarding both Local 942 and Local 267.
History
The International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Local 267 in Logansport, Pennsylvania, began as United Distillery Workers of North America, Local 942 at Logansport Distilling Company, Inc. In 1948, Local 942 renegotiated its agreement to create Local 267 Distillery Workers. Both locals had participated in the United Brewery Workers Pennsylvania Council, which lobbied for the interests of brewery and distillery workers, during their existence. The International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America merged with the Teamsters in 1973 after a lengthy battle over membership disputes.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection includes information from 1936 to 1959 regarding both United Distillery Workers of North America, Local 942, and International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America, Local 267. Correspondence and contracts are present, as well as meeting minutes. Also included are union seniority lists, constitution and by-laws, and check books. One item of note is the original certificate of affiliation between the United Distillery Workers and the Congress of Industrial Organizations from 1939.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
United Brewery Workers Local 267 Records, 1936-1959, AIS.1984.11, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
United Brewery Workers, Local 266, 1947-1979, AIS.1984.10, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh
Records of United Brewery Workers Pennsylvania Council, 1938-1983, AIS.1984.12, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh
Acquisition Information
Gift of Robert Carpen in 1984.
Logansport (Pa.); Correspondence; Brewery workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Logansport; Labor; United Brewery Workers Pennsylvania Council; Logansport Distilling Company, Inc.; United Distillery Workers of North America. Local 942 (Logansport, Pa.); International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America. Local 267 (Logansport, Pa.)
- Statement of Accounts, 1949-1955, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, National Labor Relations Board, 1949-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Legislative Correspondence, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Financial Reports, 1943, 1950-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Certificate of Union Officers for NLRB, 1949-1951, 1955-1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1941, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bills and Receipts (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Membership Assessments, 1942-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bonding Officers, 1939-1940, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Assessments of Transfers, 1941-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Income Tax Forms, 1943-1944, 1949-1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Female Employees at Logansport Distillery Company (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Contract Correspondence, 1940-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
- Regional Office Correspondence, 1954-1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Leaves of Absence, 1945-1956 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1943-1958 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
- Discharges, 1940-1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Female Seniority Roster, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Male Seniority Roster, 1947, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Names and Addresses of Male Employees, 1948, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Armstrong County Industrial Union Council Minutes, 1947-1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Financial Correspondence, 1950-1959 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Contracts, 1939-1940, 1946-1950, 1954, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 25-26)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Stamp, "United Distillery Workers L.I. Union No. 942" (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Stamp, "Distillery Workers, Local Union No. 267, Logansport, Pa." (Box 1, Folder 29)
- People's Bank of Ford City Book Issued to Local #267 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Certificate of Affiliation, Congress of Industrial Organizations, to United Distillery Workers, Local 942, March 13, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Check-off Authorizations (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Minute Book, United Distillery Workers #942, 1939-1948 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Minute Book, United Distillery Workers #942, 1948-1958 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Check Book, 1947-1949 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- People's Bank of Ford City Check Book, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- United Distillery Workers #942 Cash Book, 1936, 1939-1940, 1942-1948 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Cash Book, 1948-1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)